(Raj:)Is it me or was that Sheldon's way
of saying, "Vegas, baby"?
- I've never been there, have you?
- Me? No.
I just got "Vegas, baby!"
from Vince Vaughn in Swingers.
That could be fun, and I know
my weekend's wide open now that...
[SIGHS]
Okay, let's do this. Let's go to Las Vegas.
(Howard:)Now? Right now?
(Leonard:)Why not?
People do things right now all the time.
Why can't we be "right now" people too?
(Leonard:)Go home, pack a bag,
and we'll be "right now" people.
I have to stop at the drugstore
to refill a prescription...
(Leonard:)...but after that, we'll go right now.
- What do you say, Howard?
- I say, Vegas, baby.
- What are you gonna tell your mother?
- SeaWorld, baby.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon, are you coming?
(Sheldon:)I'd rather have a blowfly lay eggs
and hatch larvae in my auditory canal.